www.tvsubtitles.net
Does it ever end?
This is further east
than I've ever been.
( Dany speaking Dothraki )
May I present my wife
Margaery of House Tyrell?
You are very welcome
here, Lady Stark.
If Robb Stark wants a pact with us,
he should come himself.
My son is fighting a war,
not playing at one.
I cannot defeat
my brother in the field.
You must give yourself
to the Lord of Light.
I've said the words,
damn you.
( Whispers )
I will give you a son.
We've come to
a dangerous place.
My sister wants to hurt me.
She can't know about you.
Who are you?
I'm Shae, My Lady.
Your new handmaiden.
I didn't know I needed
a new handmaiden.
Catelyn: You fought bravely today,
Lady Brienne.
I fought for my king. Soon I'll
fight for him on the battlefield.
Die for him
if I must.
( Flies buzz )
You told the Queen
about my plans
- to send Myrcella to Dorne.
- Never!
Throw him in one
of the black cells.
Cersei: Myrcella is
my only daughter.
Do you really think I'll let you
sell her like a common whore?
- It's done, Cersei.
- No.
- You cannot stop it.
- No!
Not tonight.
There's another Tyrell
who requires your attention.
I'm sorry.
Do you want my brother
to come in and help?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
There's no need
for us to play games.
Save your lies for court.
You're going to need
a lot of them.
My brother Jaime rots
in a northern stockade.
Robb Stark will never
release the Kingslayer.
But his mother might.
How would you like to see
your beloved Cat again?
- Man: Outside!
- Jaqen: Come here, boy!
Sweet boy, help us.
Give it to me.
- ( Blades ring )
- ( Groans )
( Hilt thuds,
Arya grunts )
Amory:
Round up any survivors.
We'll take them back
to Harrenhal.
We're looking for
a bastard named Gendry.
You want Gendry?
You already got him.
( Theme music playing )
♪ Game of Thrones 2x04 ♪
Garden of Bones
Original Air Date on April 22, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪
( Thunder rumbling )
( Horse neighs )
It's got to be the Mountain.
He's the biggest.
- He's the strongest.
- Bulls are bigger than lions.
Doesn't mean I'd pick
a bull in a fight.
If the bull had fangs
and claws, I would.
Right, the Mountain
or our man Jaime.
- If he ever gets out.
- ( Thunderclap )
Loras Tyrell?
Loras Tyrell.
He's prettier than the queen.
I don't care about pretty.
He's better with a sword
than any of them.
How good could he be?
He's been stabbing
Renly Baratheon for years,
- and Renly ain't dead.
- ( Laughs )
( Horse whinnies )
The horses seem
a little spooked to you?
They're horses.
They get spooked
by their own shadows.
- Shh.
- ( Horse snorting )
Do you hear that?
No.
There's something
out there.
( Neighing )
- ( Farts )
- ( Gasps )
- ( Laughing )
- Oh.
Oh, you're a right
little prick.
You should see
your face.
I swear you
pissed yourself.
"Oh, who goes there?
Ahh!"
- ( Laughs )
- There is something out there.
- Yeah, don't even try me.
- ( Horse neighs )
- Rennick.
- Do you think I'm an idiot?
- Rennick!
- ( Screams )
- ( Rennick screaming )
- ( Horses neighing )
- Man: King in the North!
- Men: The King in the North!
- ( Water running )
- ( Man groans )
( Flies buzzing )
( Man #2 screaming )
( Horse neighing )
( Man #3 shouting )
Bolton: Five Lannisters dead
for every one of ours.
They're dead.
Take everything they've got.
Bolton: We've nowhere to keep
all these prisoners.
Barely enough food
to feed our own.
We're not executing
prisoners, Lord Bolton.
Of course, Your Grace.
The officers
will be useful.
Some of them may be privy
to Tywin Lannister's plans.
I doubt it.
Bolton: Well, we'll learn
soon enough.
In my family we say,
"A naked man has few secrets.
A flayed man none."
My father outlawed
flaying in the North.
- We're not in the North.
- We're not torturing them.
The high road's very pretty,
but you'll have a hard time
marching your army down it.
The Lannisters hold
prisoners of their own.
I won't give them an excuse
to abuse my sisters.
Man:
No, no, don't! Don't!
- Woman: Shh, shh.
- Please!
- Shh.
- ( Flies buzzing )
The rot's set in.
No, don't!
- Shh.
- Please, don't!
It'll get better.
It doesn't even hurt.
The rot will spread.
If we don't take the foot now--
No, you can't!
Ser! Please, Ser.
- I can't lose--
- You'll die if she does it.
I don't want to be
a cripple, please.
Surely one of our men needs your
attention more than this cub.
Your men are not
my men, My Lord.
Put this in your mouth and lie down.
You don't want to watch.
- No! You can't!
- Bite on it.
It's better than biting
your own tongue, believe me.
( Muffled screaming )
( Sawing )
- What's your name?
- Talisa.
Your last name?
You want to know what side
my family fights on?
You know my family name.
You have me at a disadvantage.
That boy lost his foot
on your orders.
They killed my father.
- That boy did?
- The family he fights for.
Do you think he's friends
with King Joffrey?
He's a fisherman's son
that grew up near Lannisport.
He probably never held a spear
before they shoved one in his
hands a few months ago.
I have no hatred
for the lad.
( Sighs )
That should help
his foot grow back.
You'd have us surrender,
end all this bloodshed.
I understand.
The country would be at peace
and life would be just
under the righteous hand
of good King Joffrey.
- You're going to kill Joffrey?
- If the Gods give me strength.
- And then what?
- I don't know.
We'll go back
to Winterfell.
I have no desire to sit
on the Iron Throne.
So who will?
I don't know.
You're fighting
to overthrow a king,
and yet you have no plan
for what comes after?
First we have
to win the war.
You never told me
where you're from.
- Volantis.
- Volantis?
You're far from home.
The boy was lucky
you were here.
He was unlucky
that you were.
You're here to answer for your
brother's latest treasons.
Your Grace,
whatever my traitor brother
has done, I had no part.
You know that.
I beg you--
Ser Lancel, tell her
of this outrage.
Lancel:
Using some vile sorcery,
your brother fell on Stafford Lannister
with an army of wolves.
( Crowd murmuring )
Thousands of good men
were butchered.
After the slaughter,
the northmen feasted on
the flesh of the slain.
( Crowd gasping, murmuring )
Killing you would send
your brother a message.
( Crying )
But my mother insists
on keeping you alive.
Stand.
So we'll have to send
your brother
a message some other way.
Meryn.
Leave her face.
I like her pretty.
- ( Blow lands )
- ( Sansa gasps )
( Groans )
Meryn, My Lady
is overdressed.
Unburden her.
If you want Robb Stark
to hear us,
we're going to have
to speak louder.
( Sobbing )
Tyrion: What is the meaning
of this?
What kind of knight
beats a helpless girl?
The kind who serves
his king, Imp.
Careful, now. We don't want
to get blood all over your
pretty white cloak.
Tyrion: Someone get the girl something
to cover herself with.
She is to be your queen.
Have you no regard
for her honor?
- Joffrey: I'm punishing her.
- Tyrion: For what crimes?
She did not fight her
brother's battle, you half-wit.
You can't talk to me like that.
The king can do as he likes!
The Mad King
did as he liked.
Has your Uncle Jaime ever told
you what happened to him?
No one threatens His Grace
in the presence of the Kingsguard.
I'm not threatening
the King, Ser.
I am educating my nephew.
Bronn, the next time
Ser Meryn speaks, kill him.
That was a threat.
See the difference?
( Crowd whispering )
Tyrion: I apologize for
my nephew's behavior.
( Crowd murmuring )
Tell me the truth.
Do you want an end
to this engagement?
I am loyal to King Joffrey,
my one true love.
Lady Stark, you may
survive us yet.
The little king's
backed up.
Clogged from balls
to brains.
You think dipping his wick
will cure what ails him?
There's no cure
for being a cunt.
But the boy's at that age.
And he's got nothing to do all
day but pick wings off flies.
Couldn't hurt to get
some of the poison out.
What are you
doing here, dog?
Your uncle left
your nameday present
and asked me to see
that you got it.
And?
What is it?
Look inside,
Your Grace.
- Happy nameday, Your Grace.
- My nameday has passed.
We won't tell
if you won't.
No.
Her.
Touch her.
( Women giggle )
( Breathing heavily )
Could you hit her?
( Laughs )
My uncle sent you?
Yes, Your Grace.
He chose us himself.
Hmm.
- ( Slapping )
- ( Laughing )
Use this.
Harder.
( Whimpers )
I said harder.
He'd want me to get
his money's worth.
( Crying )
( Screaming )
( Whimpering, crying )
Your Grace, too much pain
will spoil the pleasure.
( Woman whimpering )
Please, please,
please, Your Grace.
Your Grace,
if your uncle finds out--
Oh, I want him
to find out.
You will bring her to his
chambers when you're finished
and show him
what you've done.
Or the same thing
will happen to you.
Begin.
- ( Thuds )
- ( Screams )
Harder!
( Horse whinnies )
Well, if it isn't
my favorite whoremonger.
Pray I haven't kept
you waiting long.
Your Grace.
Now you do the Lannisters'
bidding, is that it?
Tell me, was my brother's
body even cold
before you secured
your newest patron?
I'm a practical man.
Just not a loyal one.
And who would you have
me be loyal to?
Your brother's corpse?
( Chuckles )
I don't like you,
Lord Baelish.
I don't like your face.
I don't like the words that come
oozing out of your mouth.
I don't want you in my tent
one minute more than necessary.
So tell me,
why are you here?
Renly:
You can trust Brienne.
Her loyalty comes
without charge.
You still have many friends
at court, Your Grace,
many who believe
Ned Stark erred
by not supporting
your claim.
Now I understand.
You know I have
the numbers.
You know I'm marching
on King's Landing.
When I take the throne,
you hope to retain your position.
And your head.
I would give priority
to my head.
I understand that
you don't like me,
and while that
saddens me greatly,
I did not come here today
seeking your affection.
When you march
on King's Landing,
you may find yourself facing
a protracted siege or...
open gates.
Your Grace.
Lord Baelish.
All of these tents
look the same to me.
- Would you be so kind--
- It would be my pleasure.
It took me weeks to learn
way around the camp.
Twice I walked in on officers
in stages of undress.
And the moment I learn
which tent is mine,
we're on the move again.
Your tent?
Not our tent?
The King snores, perhaps?
Or simply prefers
solitude?
Pressures of command,
no doubt.
Four kings vying
for the throne.
I am not tutored
in warfare,
but basic arithmetic favors the
side with the greater numbers.
If war were arithmetic,
the mathematicians
would rule the world.
But I did notice your brother
entering His Grace's tent the just now.
The place of a Kingsguard
is by the King's side.
And on the night
of the your wedding,
who was by
the King's side then?
You seem quite interested
in our marriage.
Your marriage
is quite interesting...
Not only to me,
but to the realm.
The marriage of a wealthy girl
always breeds interest,
if nothing else.
You've never married,
have you?
I've been unlucky
in my affections, sadly.
That is sad.
Though perhaps
it's for the best.
The whole notion of marriage
seems to confuse you,
so allow me to explain.
My husband is my King,
and my King is my husband.
Here is your tent,
Lord Baelish. Good night.
( Hoofbeats )
( Horse whinnies )
( Speaking Dothraki )
What do you know
of this place?
Only that the desert
around their walls
is called
the Garden of Bones.
Every time the Qartheen
shut their gates on a traveler,
the garden grows.
- ( Man coughing )
- ( Man #2 groans )
- Man #3: Go on!
- Man #4: You, keep moving!
( Woman crying )
- ( Screams )
- Man: Bring her about!
What kind of fire
melts stone?
Dragon fire.
There's dragons here?
No, all the dragons
are dead.
What's that smell?
Dead people.
Move.
Man:
Please, please, no, no!
( Screaming )
( Sobbing )
No.
( Screaming )
( Screaming stops )
( Chains rattle )
( Heavy thud )
Woman:
He's dead.
He was my son.
My sister
was three days ago.
My husband,
the day before that.
They take someone
every day?
Does anyone live?
( Thunder rumbling )
Arya:
Joffrey.
Cersei.
Ilyn Payne.
The Hound.
Joffrey.
Cersei.
Ilyn Payne.
The Hound.
Joffrey. Cersei.
Ilyn Payne.
The Hound.
How dare you?
You may have heard
false reports.
- You betrayed Ned.
- Betrayed?
I wanted him to serve
as Protector of the Realm.
I begged him
to seize the moment.
I trusted you.
My husband trusted you.
And you repaid our faith
with treachery.
- No, My Lady.
- Get out!
Cat, I've--
I've loved you
since I was a boy.
It seems to me that fate
has given us this chance--
Have you lost your mind?
Get out!
Do you want to see
your girls again?
Sansa, more beautiful
than ever.
And Arya,
just as wild as ever.
You have Arya, too?
Both girls are healthy
and safe...
for now.
But you know the Queen
and you know Joffrey.
I fear for
their longevity
if they remain
in the capital.
( Knife clinks )
What do you want?
The Lannisters will trade your
daughters for the Kingslayer.
Of course they will.
Jaime Lannister
for two girls?
Robb will never agree
to those terms.
I'm not bringing
these terms to him.
I'm bringing them
to you.
You think I'd keep
secrets from my son?
Robb has surprised them all
with his skills in battle,
but he's not a mother.
Consider it, Cat.
You may not get
another chance.
- I've brought you a gift.
- I don't want your gifts.
A token of Tyrion
Lannister's goodwill.
He wants you to understand
that this exchange of prisoners
is offered in good faith.
Good faith?
What's this?
Your husband was
an honorable man.
He should rest beside his family
in the crypts beneath Winterfell.
- You may not believe--
- Get out.
( Groans )
- ( Men shouting )
- Man: Get up, you dogs!
( Wood banging )
That's him,
the one who picks.
The Mountain.
What are you doing?
He told me he stares
at him every day.
That's why he
doesn't get picked.
You.
Man:
Move, boy!
Move!
( Liquid trickling )
Tickler: Is there gold and silver
in the village?
- I don't know.
- Gems?
I didn't see any.
- Where is the Brotherhood?
- I don't know.
( Rats squeaking )
( Squeaking )
- Tickler: Where is the Brotherhood?
- I don't know. Please.
- Where is the Brotherhood?
- I don't know.
- ( Rat squeaking )
- ( Whimpering )
Which of the villagers
aided them?
- I don't know.
- Who?
I--
- I never saw.
Please. Please, stop.
Please, it's starting to--
- Who?
- I didn't see anyone help him.
- ( Rat shrieking )
- Take it off! Take it off!
- Who helped him?
- Ganes the butcher
- and his son.
- That's better.
- You've been very helpful.
- No, stop, please!
What are you doing?
Please, stop!
No! No!
I told you everything!
No!
- No! ( Screaming )
- ( Rat clattering )
Joffrey.
Cersei.
Ilyn Payne.
The Hound.
Woman: Please, Polliver.
Some food.
Just a crust of bread.
( Woman crying )
Polliver.
The Mountain.
Lady Stark, I had not thought
to find you in the Stormlands.
I had not thought
to be here, Lord Stannis.
- Can that truly be you?
- Who else might it be?
When I saw your standard,
I couldn't be sure.
- Whose banner is that?
- My own.
I suppose if we used
the same one,
the battle would be
terribly confusing.
Why is your stag
on fire?
The King has taken
for his sigil
the fiery heart
of the Lord of Light.
Ah, you must be this fire
priestess we hear so much about.
Mm, brother,
now I understand why you
found religion in your old age.
Watch yourself, Renly.
Renly:
No, no, I'm relieved.
I never really believed
you're a fanatic.
Charmless, rigid,
a bore, yes,
but not a godly man.
You should kneel
he's the Lord's chosen,
born amidst salt
and smoke.
Born amidst salt
and smoke?
Is he a ham?
Stannis: That's twice
I've warned you.
Listen to yourselves.
If you were sons of mine, I
would knock your heads together
and lock you in a bedchamber
until you remembered
that you were brothers.
It is strange to find you
beside my brother, Lady Stark.
Your husband was a supporter
of my claim.
Lord Eddard's integrity
cost him his head.
And you sit beside this pretender
and chastise me.
We share a common enemy.
The Iron Throne
is mine by right.
All those that deny that
are my foes.
The whole realm denies it,
from Dorne to the Wall.
Old men deny it
with their death rattle
and unborn children deny it
in their mother's wombs.
No one wants you
for their King.
You never wanted
any friends, brother.
But a man without friends
is a man without power.
For the sake of the mother
who bore us,
I will give you this one night
to reconsider.
Strike your banners,
come to me before dawn,
and I will grant you
your old seat in the council.
I'll even name you
my heir
until a son
is born to me.
Otherwise I shall
destroy you.
Look across
those fields, brother.
Can you see
all those banners?
You think a few bolts
of cloth will make you King?
No.
The men holding those bolts
of cloth will make me King.
We shall see, Renly.
Come the dawn,
we shall see.
Look to your sins,
Lord Renly.
The night is dark
and full of terrors.
Would you believe
I loved him once?
I thought we were welcome.
If you heard a Dothraki horde
was approaching your city,
you might do the same,
Khaleesi.
Horde?
My name is Daenerys--
Daenerys Stormborn
of the House Targaryen.
You know me, My Lord?
Only by reputation,
Khaleesi.
And I'm no lord,
merely a humble merchant.
They call you
the Mother of Dragons.
And what should
I call you?
Oh, my name is quite long
and quite impossible
for foreigners to pronounce.
I am simply a trader
of spices.
But we are the Thirteen,
charged with the governance
and protection of Qarth,
the greatest city
that ever was or will be.
The beauty of
Quarth is legendary--
Qarth.
Might we see
the dragons?
My friend,
we have travelled
very far.
We have no food,
no water.
Once I see my people fed,
I would be honored--
Forgive me,
Mother of Dragons,
but no man alive has seen
a living dragon.
Some of my more
skeptical friends
refuse to believe
your children
even exist.
All we ask is the chance
to see for ourselves.
I am not a liar.
Oh, I don't think you are.
But as I've never
met you before,
my opinion on the matter
is of limited value.
Where I come from,
guests are treated
with respect,
not insulted
at the gates.
Then perhaps you should
return to where you come from.
We wish you well.
What are you doing?
You promised
to receive me.
We have received you.
Here we are,
and here you are.
If you do not let us in,
all of us will die.
Which we shall
deeply regret.
But Qarth did not become
the greatest city that
ever was or will be
by letting Dothraki savages
through its gates.
Khaleesi, please
be careful.
Thirteen!
When my dragons are grown,
we will take back
what was stolen from me
and destroy those
who have wronged me.
We will lay waste
to armies
and burn cities
to the ground.
Turn us away and we will
burn you first.
Ah.
You are a true
Targaryen.
Only, as you said
a moment ago,
if we don't let you
into the city,
you will all die.
And so...
Retreating in fear
from a little girl
is unbecoming
of the greatest city
that ever was
or will be.
The discussion is over,
Xaro Xhoan Daxos.
The Thirteen have spoken.
I am one of the Thirteen
and I am still speaking.
The girl threatens to burn
our city to the ground
and you would invite her in
for a cup of wine?
She is the Mother
of Dragons.
Do you expect her to watch
her people starve
without breathing fire?
I believe we can allow
a few Dothraki
through our gates
without dooming our city.
After all, here I am,
a savage from
the Summer Isles,
and Qarth still stands.
Our decision is final.
Very well.
I invoke Soumai.
I will vouch for her,
her people,
and her dragons
in accordance with the law.
Be it on your head.
Welcome to Qarth,
My Lady.
Mountain:
You.
Tickler: Is there gold or silver
in the village?
- I'm not from the village.
- Where is the Brotherhood?
I don't know
what that is.
( Squeaking )
( Horses neigh )
Man: You two, take Lord Lannister's
things to his quarters.
What's this?
We weren't expecting you
till tomorrow, Lord Tywin.
( Chuckles )
Evidently not.
Why are these prisoners
not in their cells?
Mountain: Cells are overflowing,
My Lord.
Polliver:
This lot won't be here long.
Don't need
no permanent place.
After we interrogate 'em,
we usually just...
Are we so well-manned
that we can afford to discard
able young bodies
and skilled laborers?
You,
do you have a trade?
Gendry:
Smith, My Lord.
What are you looking at?
Kneel!
Kneel or I'll carve
your lungs out, boy.
He'll do no such thing.
This one's a girl,
you idiot,
dressed as a boy.
- Why?
- Safer to travel, My Lord.
Smart.
More than I can say
for this lot.
Get these prisoners
to work.
Bring the girl.
I need a new
cupbearer.
Mountain:
My Lord.
( Knocking on door )
Your visits
are too few, cousin.
Her Grace,
the Queen Regent,
commands you to release
Grand Maester Pycelle.
- Here's your warrant.
- So it is.
Will you take
a cup with me?
I find that mulled wine
helps me sleep.
I am here
at Her Grace's behest,
not to drink
with you, Imp.
If my sister was
so concerned for Pycelle,
I would have thought
she'd come herself.
Instead she sends you.
What am I to make
of that?
I don't care
what you make of it,
so long as you release
your prisoner immediately.
And you've received these
instructions directly from Cersei?
As I said several times.
And you've waited this long
to deliver the information?
When the Queen Regent
gives me a command, I carry
it out without delay.
Cersei must have
great trust in you,
allowing you
into her chamber
during the hour
of the wolf.
The Queen Regent has a great
many responsibilities.
She often works
from dusk till dawn.
She must be very glad
to have you helping her
from dusk till dawn.
Ah, lavender oil.
She always loved lavender oil,
even as a girl.
I am a knight!
An anointed knight, yes.
Tell me, did Cersei
have you knighted
before or after she took
you into her bed?
What?
Nothing to say?
No more warnings
for me, Ser?
You will withdraw
these filthy accusations.
Have you ever given
any thought
to what King Joffrey
will have to say
when he finds out you've
been bedding his mother?
It's not my fault!
Did she take you
against your will?
Can you not defend
yourself, knight?
Your own father, Lord Tywin,
when I was named the King's squire,
he told me to obey her
in everything.
Did he tell you
to fuck her, too?
I only meant
I did as I was bid.
Hated every
moment of it,
is that what you'll
have me believe?
A high place in court,
a knighthood,
my sister's legs spreading
open for you at night.
Oh, yes, it must
have been terrible.
Wait here. His Grace will want
to hear this.
Mercy!
Mercy, My Lord! I beg you.
Save it for Joffrey.
He loves a good grovel.
My Lord, it was
your sister's bidding--
the Queen.
I'll leave the city
at once, I swear.
- No, I think not.
- My Lord?
You heard me.
My father told you
to obey my sister.
Obey her.
Stay close to her side.
Keep her trust.
Pleasure her
whenever she requires.
No one ever need know
as long as you keep
faith with me.
I want to know
what Cersei is doing,
where she goes,
who she sees,
what they talk of--
everything.
And you will tell me.
Yes, My Lord, I will.
I swear it,
as you command.
Oh, rise, rise.
Let us drink to
our understanding.
Oh, you don't have
a cup. Oh, well.
Smile, cousin. My sister
is a beautiful woman.
And it's all for
the good of the realm.
Go back and tell her
that I beg her forgiveness,
that I want no more
conflict between us
and that henceforth
I shall do nothing
without her consent.
But her demands.
Oh, I'll give her Pycelle.
- You will?
- Yes, I'll release him in the morning.
Cersei can keep him
as a pet if she wants,
but I will not have him
on the council.
I could swear that I had not
harmed a single hair on his head,
but that would not,
strictly speaking, be true.
( Wood creaking )
( Waves crashing )
Man: Stay within
one table length.
Your Grace.
Do your knucklebones
bring you luck?
Well, life's been good since you
hacked them off, Your Grace.
And it's four less
fingernails to clean.
- Fewer.
- Pardon?
Four fewer
fingernails to clean.
Never understood
why you had to wear them.
It reminds me of where I
come from and where I am now.
It reminds me
of your justice.
It was an honest
punishment
and you were good
with the cleaver.
You were a hero
and a smuggler.
A good act does not
wash out the bad,
nor a bad the good.
A lesson I've tried
to teach my son.
- Does he listen?
- To me?
Gods, no.
But if your red woman told him
to leap from the crow's nest--
She has a name.
I trust you've not forgotten
your smuggler's tricks.
I've lived within
the law for 17--
I want you to be
a smuggler this time.
Any shore, any night.
What am I bringing
ashore?
The red woman.
No one must know
what you do
and we'll not speak
of this again.
I am true to Your Grace
and always will be,
but surely there are
other ways, cleaner ways.
Cleaner ways
don't win wars.
Are you afraid,
onion knight?
Someone once told me
the night is dark and
full of terrors.
You've carried more
unpleasant cargo in your time.
Are you a good man,
Ser Davos Seaworth?
I'd say my parts
are mixed, My Lady--
good and bad.
If half an onion
is black with rot,
it's a rotten onion.
A man is good
or he is evil.
- And which are you?
- Oh, good.
I'm a knight myself
of sorts,
a champion of light
and life.
Well, that must be
very nice for you.
- Do you love your wife?
- I do.
Yet you have known
other women.
Don't talk about my wife.
I'm not. I'm talking about
other women.
Like me, Ser Davos.
You want me.
You want to see
what's beneath this robe.
And you will.
Strange that
this Lord of Light
asks you to work
in the shadows.
Shadows cannot live
in the dark, Ser Davos.
They are servants
of light,
the children of fire.
And the brighter the flame,
the darker they are.
These weren't here before.
They've barred the passage.
( Chuckles )
They can't bar
our passage.
Gods protect us.
There's only one God,
Ser Davos,
and he only protects
those who serve him.
( Gasps )
( Laughs, gasps )
( Moaning )
( Moans )
( Screaming )
( Shrieking )
( Growls )
( Theme music playing )
== sync, corrected by elderman ==